hello everyone welcome back to the
channel the trading game the channel
where you get all the stock market
related information news and financial
education
in this video we'll be talking about
what a fun idea so we'll be doing the
throw analysis of this particular stock
okay before that let's uh as usual let's
look into today's market update how the
market be here today
so uh let's start with uh nifty so you
can see
nifty is up today with the 120 points at
1.11 percentage
and the run is continuing on the upside
continuously the market is
going upside and looking at the details
as you can see here uh
there was uh friday's closure was 10 900
and today it opened almost 100 points
gap which is
huge almost of one percentage from there
it made a low of 1053 but at the second
of as usual in the last few days
whatever it is doing
the same thing it did when it jumped
higher and
it made a high of 11 037 and almost it
closed at the day high which is at 11
0.22
making it a higher of 1.1 percentage for
the day compared to the
previous close which is on friday's
close and uh coming to bank nifty update
so the same thing happened here also
wherein bank nifty jumped at 355 points
on the upside
making 1.62 percentage compared to
friday's closure
and uh you can see here uh a previous
early it closed at 21.96 meaning i
closed up below that 22 000 mark and
today it opened
22 000 307 which means 300 plus points
gap up
in in fact almost 350 points gap up
but from there it made a low of 22 187
but uh and high also 22 520 and it
closed
in between almost at the opening price
which is
22 321 making it as 1.62 percentage
okay so now we will look into a few of
the guinness and losers
top guinness of the day and uh before
that
my humble request to all the new people
here is that
if you are a new heroes please do
subscribe the channel so that
it gives me some motivation for doing
further videos and uh please hit that
like button
okay so looking at the gainers adani
enterprises
is the heavy gainer with a six
percentage movement
and bajaj finance gained four point two
five percent
and at the last moment you can see a
heavy buying came up in it stocks where
in hcl tech mode
four percentage and the tech main also
moved around
three point eight six percentage and the
upl was the other gainer
with almost four percentage so coming to
the losers
you can see here the top four out of
five the top four stocks are from the
farmer category uh wherein sun forma is
leading the fall wherein it
fell four percent and lupine is around
three point seven percentage and
glen mark fell two point six percentage
and the ziploc
around two percentage again and india
also closed at
exactly two percentage okay with that
let's look into the analysis of this
vodafone idea so we'll be going through
the chart and we'll be looking into all
the details of the stock
so here we are into the daily chart of
vodafone idea
and it as you can see here i have
applied a
60 ema for this particular stock and
you can see this red line is nothing but
this is a 60 ema
and for the new people here who are
asking why 60 ama
because every particular stock
follows one particular indicator meaning
there is no particular indicator which
works good on everything so we need to
find out that particular indicator which
works good on a stock
so similarly 60 ema is a very good
indicator for this stock
so if you are a new old subscriber into
my channel uh probably you might be
knowing that on this particular day
20 or yeah i think on 20th
uh may i had prepared a video on this
stock wherein i gave clearly a buying
indication for this stock which was
around
5.6 then and uh you you
you saw how how much it rallied and i
will be you can find the same video
in the upside i button there so that you
can
exactly come to know what exactly was
the video and uh
how the stock behaved after that okay so
at this point i had given a buy signal
and
just for the new people we'll just go
back and we will look into how
exactly this is uh behaving with that uh
60 ema
so let's uh let's look into might be a
december timeframe
so december it was on the upside of this
line
and it tried crossing here but it was a
failure but once when
it crossed this line you can see again
it tried
touching that and going on the opposite
side but it was a failure and from there
it continuously fell again from there it
tried crossing that with some
news coming in but it was a failure and
but after that you can see it was uh
for some time it was just trading here
in some channel
and once that broke around this mid
i i gave a call on this uh wherein i
said that
a huge move is coming in this particular
stock
and you can see how big the stock is
moved and
now after this all moment now it is
again
back to the same original 60 mark
so what next so as you can see here
it was initially on the upside of this
line
and basically it tried crossing that but
it was a failure and again yesterday you
can see that
it it tried moving totally on the again
against and it closed at the higher but
you can see today's channel today's
candle is kind of something
it is not clear because even though
even though it has closed uh above
yesterday's price but a red candle is
kind of indicating
so now what i'm saying here is as of now
for me the stock is clearly in a
downtrend because
i'm not getting that confirmation for
the stock to move up
because even though yesterday it was a
green candle here or
today after opening it close it closed
uh
i mean it closed on the negative side so
for me uh
as as long as the stock doesn't cross
this
9.7 which is or today's high i'll be on
a bearish side
for this particular stock and my target
will be around this particular area
because this is a
immediate support for this which is
around 6.2
unless it crosses that and it gives an
indication for me that
it was a fake move here right this
particular
these three candles which which i
particularly looking at this graph and
uh
with my experience for the last 10 years
in the market what i'm seeing here is
it might come down and it might
it might just the next target for this
talk will be around this
six plus uh area okay uh and by chance
if it
crosses this 9.7 mark tomorrow so then
probably we can look into buying
but as of now my personal wave is i'll
be shorting this stock with a very
minimal
uh stop off around um say currently it
is
trading at nine maybe around the sixty
pisces seventy percent
from here which is around the nine point
seven or nine point eight
the max from there i'll be looking for a
target of
6.2 because what i'm saying here is from
here when it is coming down
so there are chances that it will break
this ema and
can fall further from here okay so
with that let me conclude the video and
uh again my humble request to the new
people here please if you are
new here please do subscribe the channel
if you find that
if you found that something you have
learned from this video and uh for
making other further
videos it will be a big motivation for
me
for your subscription and you are like
okay
with that let's meet in the next video
until then take care see you